Muhammad Hamza Khan

Full Stack MERN, Angular Developer

I am ambitious, visionary and goal-oriented. I thrive on challenges and want to go experiences where I can continuously learn and grow. I envision my life to be spent in great contribution to humanity and the world through science and technology.



hamzahere52@gmail.com

+923017796315

Islamabad

linkedin.com/in/hamzakhanhere

github.com/Hamzakhan001

EDUCATION

Geo-Informatics Systems Engineering Institute of Geographical Information System Engineering(IGIS), NUST

09/2018 - 06/2022

Islamahad

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Wavloader

 This project is a Map oriented project management software designed for Real Estate Industry where user can manage their projects, check blockers, create day to day tasks as workitems, change their status & location, check live streaming, manage their projects actual location, create buffer zones etc that gives user power to manage project using this software

ARMS

 This is real estate digital software where client can check available properties, book meetings, have property tour, select different financial models and book a contract with company and transfer property. This software truly digitise real estate system.

Feasibility Web Application

This application let the user find best suitable location for any specifc business based on analaysis on the. App was developed using MERN stack

Developer Social Media Application

 I used MERN stack for this social media application where developers can socialize with other developers

E-commerce Application using MERN stack and Rect & Django

• This E-commerce application has all features on any working Ecommerce platform i.e Data display added by admin, images, top sold items feature on top, cart, prices addition in cart and local storage usage for checkout.

Land Surveying Application (04/2021 - 04/2021)

This is a full stack web application using openlayers, ajax, geoserver and postgis that carry the potential of being used by any commercial entity. User can mark location of important features as point, line or polygon along with important information associated with it

Web-GIS Based Data Visualization and Statistics

• This is Web & GIS based data visualization application where data against entered coordinates can be entered and can analyzed against different dates with maps and bar and gantt charts

Covid Dashboard (08/2020 - 08/2020)

 Made covid dashboard using data provided by WHO that user can use to analyse situation of covid in world

Normalized Difference Vegetation Index(NDVI) of satellite Imagery using Python Libraries

GDAL, Numpy, GeoPandas and Shapely

SKILLS

MERN Stack

Typescript

React

Angular

Javascript(Node Js, Google Earth Engine)

Databases(PostgreSQL/PostGIS/MySQL/MongoDB)

Python(Django RF, Flask, Fast API)

Datavisualization(Tableau, Microsoft Excel, Power BI)

Mapping Libraries(Leaflet, React-Leaflet, Mapbox, OpenLayers)

Geemap

Machine Learning

Deep Learning

GeoServer

Google Earth Engine

WORK EXPERIENCE

GagaMuller Technology (09/2022 - Present)

Working as a Web developer here. I work mostly on Angular using typescript for this project management platform

Graana.com

I developed feasibility web application using MERN that allows user to get best suitable sites for business based on data & worked on project that automates end to end real estate journey from property display to financials, contracts and legals.

Full Stack Web Developer GIS Plus(NUST)

I worked with team as a web developer on their web mapping project both on front and backend developement. Implemented map popup feature based on react and APIs that were made in Node Js.

Full Stack Web Developer and Project Management Intern

Worked on Car Block Application and Project Management Internee at Car Block Application

Final Year Project

We are developing a Geo-Marketing Platform where client can upload ad content and get best suited location based on targeted audience and description to maximize reach of ad-content. We are also developing a dashboard to visualize ad campaigns insights. Technologies used are: React Js, Node js, Postgres/PostGIS

CERTIFICATES

Udacity Cloud Native Program Persuina

Udacity AWS Machine Learning Nanodegree Persuing